No, see, the liquid-metal terminators
were created in the future by Skynet...
(Leonard:)...and Skynet was developed
by Miles Dyson...
(Leonard:)...but that future no longer exists
due to Dyson's death in Terminator 2.
(Sheldon:)Okay, then riddle me this.
(Sheldon:)Assuming all the good terminators...
(Sheldon:)...were originally evil terminators
created by Skynet...
(Sheldon:)...then reprogrammed by the future
John Connor, why would Skynet...
(Sheldon:)...an artificial computer intelligence...
(Sheldon:)...bother to create
a petite, hot, 17-year-old killer robot?
(Leonard:)Skynet is kinky? I don't know.
(Sheldon:)Artificial intelligences
do not have teen fetishes.
- All right, wait. They use it to lure...
- Eh! Too late, I win.
[PENNY SINGING "OUT TONIGHT"]
Let's go out tonight
I have to go out tonight
(Leonard:)What the hell is that?
(Sheldon:)I don't know. But if cats could sing...